<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-05-19T20:52:29-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">optimism.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/05/15/optimism.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="optimism." /><published>2023-05-15T22:57:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-05-15T22:57:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/05/15/optimism</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/05/15/optimism.html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been busy with procrastinating on assignments and getting rejected from internships to properly commit time to this blog, so apologies for not writing for so long to my nonexistent readers. I will hopefully change that over this summer, but I’ll only write about stuff when I feel like it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s so much stuff that’s been going on since I last wrote in here! I just finished my second year of college, and I’m on track to graduate next year. Classes have been pretty hard and I’m not doing the best that I could in them, but I don’t really care – I feel like I went to college more for experiencing things and less for getting good grades in my college. I feel more fulfilled than I ever have in my entire life; I’m about to head to my first internship with a semiconductor manufacturer in Minneapolis for this summer, and I have a list of goals to complete, as well!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get a return offer from my summer internship.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get an A in the one summer class I’m taking.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get an internship in Summer ’24.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gain ten pounds, which means going from 130-&amp;gt;140 lb by the end of summer.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Prepare for my two hardest classes this fall.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have an actual product for me and my friends’ side project that we can demo by the end of the summer.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wake up at 6 AM every day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know I was sad about my relationships in my last post, but that has drastically changed over these two years. I couldn’t be happier with all my friends now; they’re funny as fuck and just all-around good people. I also got a girlfriend! She’s super cool and gorgeous and sweet and funny and I think she’s just amazing. Life honestly couldn’t be better right now – could it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See, the thing is, I know my life right now is objectively way better than a year or two ago, but the thing is I KNOW it can get better than this. All my hard work led to this internship, and me learning how to actually deal with people in general helped me grow a huge amount in my personal life. But now I feel like the sky’s the limit for me; these last few years have been a proof of concept that becoming a better person is not out of reach for me. I feel like this summer will be very conducive to my growth, what with the only things me being able to do are my internship and working out. I really do feel like I’ll come out of this summer a better person – somebody who I can be confident in, his abilities and purpose honed to a finer point than now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">I’ve been busy with procrastinating on assignments and getting rejected from internships to properly commit time to this blog, so apologies for not writing for so long to my nonexistent readers. I will hopefully change that over this summer, but I’ll only write about stuff when I feel like it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">feels.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/10/21/feels.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="feels." /><published>2021-10-21T23:28:06-05:00</published><updated>2021-10-21T23:28:06-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/10/21/feels</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/10/21/feels.html">&lt;p&gt;I’m going to sleep at 2 A.M. while thinking about the assignments piling up this week, and I had a sobering thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t recall the last time I’ve been truly happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure, I’ve had my achievements and awards, but in the moment, I’ve always thought about if I had done this better or this sooner, I would have been better off. An example? How about the time I got accepted to the school I’m attending right now, the University of Wisconsin? I’m sitting at my computer, staring at the acceptance letter, and I’m FUCKING THINKING about not getting accepted into a better college, and having to “settle” for this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What even is happiness, anyway? Certain stimuli trigger the release of dopamine in our brain, and that makes us feel good. I already know that you can’t always be happy — if that was the case, happiness would lose its meaning, like in The Giver. You need to experience sadness to truly appreciate the beauty of happiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a pretty toxic friend group in high school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t that everything they said to me was negative, it’s just that nothing they said to me registered as good. So at the time, I did not perceive the friendships I had as necessarily negative (spoiler alert: they were), but just as something. And I thought that was the norm, until I came to this school and met people who genuinely cared about my emotional well-being. I honestly don’t know how I would have turned out if I continued to have friends that constantly shit on me and justified it as “banter” — probably a sociopath who hated everyone and manipulated them for their own amusement. Actually, never mind — I don’t think I’d be smart enough to do that. I’d probably just turn into a misanthropist. But yeah, most of my friends in high school were pretty shitty people in general — I just didn’t see it at the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crux of it is, I don’t really know how to be happy. I have some ideas, but I don’t know if they’ll work or not. For now, I’ll focus on the simplest one, building my self-confidence. I’m going to try to go to the gym more often — not skip a few days and go when I feel like it, but force myself to make it a painful routine, then a habit, then a reward. I’ve always been a bit insecure about my body, since I’m like severely underweight and also lowkey look like a stick, so I’m hoping that a better body will equate to me thinking better about myself (as well as helping me realize that effort yields results), therefore boosting my self-esteem. Side note: I also think the validation from my new friends about my appearance and my personality is also really helping me build it up, so if one of you sees this, keep that up; it’s really helping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know it’ll be hard to do, but if I try, I’ll be okay for sure.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">I’m going to sleep at 2 A.M. while thinking about the assignments piling up this week, and I had a sobering thought.</summary></entry></feed>